[
    {
        "front": "アニメ",
        "back": "anime",
        "chapter": "N4 C17"
    },
    {
        "front": "まんが",
        "back": "manga",
        "chapter": "N4 C17"
    },
    {
        "front": "うける",
        "back": "to take",
        "chapter": "N4 C17"
    },
    {
        "front": "インターネット",
        "back": "internet",
        "chapter": "N4 C17"
    },
    {
        "front": "しらべる",
        "back": "to look up; to do research on",
        "chapter": "N4 C17"
    },
    {
        "front": "たとえば",
        "back": "for example",
        "chapter": "N4 C17"
    },
    {
        "front": "つごう",
        "back": "convenience",
        "chapter": "N4 C17"
    },
    {
        "front": "きけん",
        "back": "dangerous",
        "chapter": "N4 C17"
    },
    {
        "front": "あんぜん",
        "back": "safe",
        "chapter": "N4 C17"
    },
    {
        "front": "せつめい（する）",
        "back": "explanation / to explain",
        "chapter": "N4 C17"
    },
    {
        "front": "ただしい",
        "back": "correct",
        "chapter": "N4 C17"
    },
    {
        "front": "ひく",
        "back": "to search for (in dict.)",
        "chapter": "N4 C17"
    },
    {
        "front": "しらべる",
        "back": "to look up (in dict.)",
        "chapter": "N4 C17"
    },
    {
        "front": "チェックする",
        "back": "to check (on internet)",
        "chapter": "N4 C17"
    },
    {
        "front": "さがす",
        "back": "to look for (on internet)",
        "chapter": "N4 C17"
    },
    {
        "front": "みつける",
        "back": "to find (on internet)",
        "chapter": "N4 C17"
    },
    {
        "front": "のっている",
        "back": "(words) to be on a dictionary",
        "chapter": "N4 C17"
    }
]